Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
- Arnold Petersen, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: How to build a sane world, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 13: Socialism: Champion of Civilized Principles, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Capitalism is no bargain!, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: Automation: What must workers do about it?, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Strikes and the 'public', Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 17: Common sense and the h-bomb, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 18: War Why?, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 19: What means this strike?, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: The Union 'Jack' built, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Peace, Plenty, Freedom, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 22: Race prejudicewhy?, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 23: Socialism: champion of civilized principles, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 24: You've read the lies about socialism...now read the facts, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 25: Socialist Industrial Unionism, the Workers' power; Greatest robbery in history; Who speaks for Socialism?, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 26: To the Members of the NEC of the Socialist Labor party, Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
  - Item 27: The Ithaca Socialist, 1993; Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
    Notes: Mar-93
  - Item 28: The Ithaca Socialist, 1995; Publication (Box 337, Folder 4)
    Notes: Summer 1995
  - Item 29: The People Library, 1900-1901 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.2:no. 6-9, 11, 19-21 (Issues bound together)
- Arnold Petersen, Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Daniel De Leon, internationalist, 1948; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Proletarian democracy vs. dictatorships and despotism, 1937; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Capital and labor, 1939; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Proletarian democracy vs. dictatorships and despotism, 1955; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Socialism; the world of tomorrow, 1939; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: W.Z. Foster--renegade or spy?, 1945; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: De Leon the uncompromising, 1939; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Daniel de Leon. Pioneer socialist editor, 1937; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Daniel De Leon, social scientist, 1945; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: Daniel De Leon, orator, 1942; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: De Leonist milestones, 1952; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Stalinist corruption of Marxism, 1940; Publication (Box 337, Folder 5)
- Socialist Party (U.S.), Publication (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Incentive pay: the speed-up new style, 1945; Publication (Box 338, Folder 1)
    Author: Albert Gates
  - Item 2: Unions face the Depression, 1938; Publication (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Socialism, the hope of humanity, 1945; Publication (Box 338, Folder 1)
    Author: Max Schachtman
  - Item 4: Marxism versus Soviet Despotism, 1959; Publication (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Is it a crime to be old?, Publication (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: What is socialism?, Publication (Box 338, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Parable of the water tank, Publication (Box 338, Folder 1)
- Socialist Workers Party, Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Jobs for all: a fighting program for labor, 1945; Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
    Author: Art Preis
  - Item 2: Fight the slave labor law!: statement of National Committee of the Socialist Workers Party., 1947; Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The struggle for negro equality, 1943; Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
    Author: John Saunders
  - Item 4: Build a labor party now, 1946; Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
    Author: George Clarke
  - Item 5: The Socialist Workers Party: what it is, what it stands for, 1948; Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
    Author: Joseph Hansen
  - Item 6: Labor's answer to conscription, 1940; Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
    Author: Felix Morrow
  - Item 7: A practical program to kill Jim Crow, 1945; Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
    Author: Charles Jackson
  - Item 8: Socialist Review, 1938; Publication (Box 338, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 6, no.6 (May-June 1938)
- Workers Party of the United States. National Committee., Publication (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The movement for world trade union unity, 1925; Publication (Box 338, Folder 3)
    Author: Thomas Bell
  - Item 2: A program of action; veterans and labor., 1946; Publication (Box 338, Folder 3)
    Author: Charles Carsten
  - Item 3: Poems for workers: an anthology, 1925; Publication (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Security and a living wage: a statement, 1945; Publication (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: An Appeal to the toilers of the Marine Industry, Publication (Box 338, Folder 3)
    Notes: Photocopy
  - Item 6: Stop the enemies of the working people, 1947; Publication (Box 338, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Vote for Southern Members of Congress on Major Legislation 75th Congress, 1937; Publication (Box 338, Folder 3)
- Southern Regional Council, Inc., Publication (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Minimum Wage Campaign Kit, Publication (Box 338, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Correspondence - Re: Minimum Wage Campaign Kit, Publication (Box 338, Folder 4)
- Moving Picture Machine Operators, Salt Lake, Publication (Box 338, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 50th Anniversary Commemorative Journal, 1962; Publication (Box 338, Folder 5)
- Exhibition Employees Local 829, Publication (Box 338, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Ree Office News, 1951; Publication (Box 338, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.1: no.1 (March 1951)
  - Item 2: Pension fund booklet, Publication (Box 338, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Welfare fund booklet, Publication (Box 338, Folder 6)
- Motion Picture Costumers, Local 705, Publication (Box 338, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Costumer, 1953; Publication (Box 338, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8:no.8-11 (1953)
  - Item 2: The Costumer, 1953; Publication (Box 338, Folder 7)
    Notes: Souvenir Program
- International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees and Moving Picture Machine Operators of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report of the Board of Trustees, 1946; Publication (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: General Bulletin no. 19, 1920; Publication (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The Government of the United States gives you the Factcs!, 1945; Publication (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Proceedings of the Tenth District., 1946; Publication (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Pension and Welfare funds, 1957; Publication (Box 338, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Legislative Committee's Report (annual) of the Tenth District, 1947; Publication (Box 338, Folder 8)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 339, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: AFSCME Insight, 1967-1969 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1;no.1,3-8
  - Item 2: AFSCME Insight, 1967-1969 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-7,9-10
  - Item 3: AFSCME Insight, 1967-1969 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.1-5-8,10-12
  - Item 4: AFSCME Insight, 1967-1969 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.4:no. 1
  - Item 5: AFSCME Insight, 1967-1969 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    Notes: Special Issue
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Facing the future: AFSCME's approach to technology, 1985; Publication (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Dues paying professional, Publication (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Correspondence, 1954; Publication (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Correspondence, 1956; Publication (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Retirement System for State Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 339, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: OASI - How to calculate benefits, 1954; Publication (Box 339, Folder 2)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Legislative Conference, Goals for 1978, 1977; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Political Action Campaign Course III (Fall 1977), Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Recognize a friend?, 1977; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Michigan Public Employees, the largest Public Employee Council in the world..., 1977; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: In the best spirit of the Democratic Process, Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: District Council 37 Political Action, Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Daily Noose, New York's Peculiar Newspaper, 1974; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 436 (1974)
  - Item 8: NYPL Library Guild Local 1930 Newsletter, 1973; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
    Notes: Feb, Apr, Nov. 1973
  - Item 9: NYPL Library Guild Local 1930 Newsletter, 1974; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
    Notes: May, Aug, Dec 1974
  - Item 10: DC 37: 100,000, Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: How to prepare for a successful get out the vote drive, 1973; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Public Employee Press, 1975; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.16:no.15, 17
  - Item 13: Press Release - "Gotbaum supports Moynihan", 1976; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Political Action News, 1978; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 2
  - Item 15: To New York District Councils - A report on Federal Legislative activities, 1977; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Political action and legislation Campaign Course II, 1977; Publication (Box 339, Folder 3)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: This is District Council 37: State, County, Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, New York City, Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Health and security benefits for Hospital Employees of the City of New York. Beneficios de Salud y Seguridad para Los Empleados de los Hospitales, Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
    Language: English;Spanish.
  - Item 3: Leave rules for Municipal Employees, City of New York: effective July 1, 1967, through June 30, 1970, Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Report of the Tri-Partite Panel: on collective bargaining procedures in Public Employment, 1966; Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: DC 37 explains your pension: facts and advice on New York City Employees Retirement System: career pension plan, 55-year increased service fraction plan, Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Public Employee Press, 1969; Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.10:no.15
  - Item 7: City-Wide contract between - City of New York and District Council 37, 1967; Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Let's hear it for Wall St. and some other beautiful people, 1975; Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
    Notes: Flyer. 2 copies
  - Item 9: DC 37 Staff Assignments, 1964; Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Statement of Calogero Taibi, special representative, District Council 37, 1961; Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: DC 37 1044-1969 - The fighting union of City Employees - 25 years young, Publication (Box 339, Folder 4)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 339, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Health and welfare plans for Public Employees financed in whole or in part by the employer, 1960; Publication (Box 339, Folder 5)
    Notes: April 1960. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Health and welfare plans for Public Employees financed in whole or in part by the employer, 1962; Publication (Box 339, Folder 5)
    Notes: July, 1962. 2 copies
  - Item 3: America's child care needs: the 1987 AFSCME National Secretaries Week, Opinion Poll, Publication (Box 339, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: How to choose child care, Publication (Box 339, Folder 5)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 339, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: DPUI Employee, 1941; Publication (Box 339, Folder 6)
    Notes: Oct, Dec 1941
  - Item 2: DPUI Employee, 1942; Publication (Box 339, Folder 6)
    Notes: Jan, Mar 1942
  - Item 3: The Employee, 1941; Publication (Box 339, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.20-21, 23-24, 26
  - Item 4: The Employee, 1942; Publication (Box 339, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.1
  - Item 5: Proposed amendments to the New York State Unemployment Insurance Law, 1938; Publication (Box 339, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Presentation to the Joint Legislative Committee investigating the Administration of Unemployment Insurance in the Dept. of Labor - State of New York, 1939; Publication (Box 339, Folder 6)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 339, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Leadership Conference Illinois State Employees Council No. 34, 1956; Publication (Box 339, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Retirement System for State Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 339, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Bulletin to all Illinois Union Members, 1955; Publication (Box 339, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: DPUI Employee, 1941; Publication (Box 339, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan., Mar.-July, Sept.-Dec. 1941
  - Item 5: DPUI Employee, 1940; Publication (Box 339, Folder 7)
    Notes: Dec. 1940
  - Item 6: An outline of recent changes in State Employees Retirement Laws., 1953; Publication (Box 339, Folder 7)
- New York Public Library Guild, Publication (Box 339, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Local Line, 1971; Publication (Box 339, Folder 8)
    Notes: July-Dec. 1971
  - Item 2: The Local Line, 1972; Publication (Box 339, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-May, July, Dec. 1972
  - Item 3: The Local Line, 1975; Publication (Box 339, Folder 8)
    Notes: Mar. 1975
  - Item 4: NYPL Library Guild Local 1930 Newsletter, 1971; Publication (Box 339, Folder 8)
    Notes: Oct. 1971
  - Item 5: NYPL Library Guild Local 1930 Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 339, Folder 8)
    Notes: Feb., Mar., May-June 1972
  - Item 6: NYPL Library Guild Local 1930 Newsletter, 1975; Publication (Box 339, Folder 8)
    Notes: Apr., Aug.-Sept. 1975
  - Item 7: The foreward look and thinking in government, 1957; Publication (Box 339, Folder 8)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 340, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: William Lucy, 1977; Publication (Box 340, Folder 1)
    Notes: News Release
  - Item 2: Jerry Wurf, 1977; Publication (Box 340, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Jack Conway, 1977; Publication (Box 340, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: William W. Hamilton, Jr., 1977; Publication (Box 340, Folder 1)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The shop steward, key to a strong union, 1958; Publication (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Your union, Publication (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Officers manual, 1946; Publication (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: You've come a long way-maybe: a working woman's guide to pay equity., 1983; Publication (Box 340, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Mental Illness can be cured, 1947; Publication (Box 340, Folder 2)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Pension Primer, 1939; Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Education for one world: jobs, security, peace, 1945; Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Teachers, Parents, Trade Unions, Civic and Community Organizaitons, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Financing the schools, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: To Private School Tachers!, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Call to a conference on the Junior High Schools, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Roosevelt message to Congress, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Music lessons for everyone, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: A letter to supervisors in the NYC School system, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: To the College staff in the Metropolitan area, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: A new charter for education - how should the Friedsam Formula for State Aid be revised?, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: The teachers union invites you to join the CIO, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Dear substitute, if, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Music Teachers are in the CIO!, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Introducing the Union of City Employees, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: 1944 - A challenge to teachers, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Our investment in tomorrow, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Not all the children receive an equal education, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Meet the CIO, Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: The right to a good education, 1944; Publication (Box 340, Folder 3)
- Brooklyn Library Guild Local 1482, Publication (Box 340, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Library Guild Voice, 1967; Publication (Box 340, Folder 4)
    Notes: June-July 1967
  - Item 2: Library Guild Voice, 1968; Publication (Box 340, Folder 4)
    Notes: July, Nov. 1968
  - Item 3: Library Guild Voice, 1969; Publication (Box 340, Folder 4)
    Notes: Jan., Apr., June, Sept., Nov.- Dec. 1969
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 340, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The struggle for the union at YWCA, 1950; Publication (Box 340, Folder 5)
    Author: Winnifred Wygal
  - Item 2: Professional workers as trade unionists, 1959; Publication (Box 340, Folder 5)
    Author: John A. Fitch
  - Item 3: Unions in the profession of social work, by Arthur Katz, and A professional views the union, by Jack R. Goldberg, 1959; Publication (Box 340, Folder 5)
    Author: Arthur Katz; Jack R. Goldberg
  - Item 4: You and CSAE, Publication (Box 340, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Free Labor Acts, Publication (Box 340, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: The Dignity of people, Publication (Box 340, Folder 5)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Librarians' Guild Communicator, 1969; Publication (Box 340, Folder 6)
    Notes: Mar.-Apr. 1969
  - Item 2: Selected bibliography: the Development of Unions in Libraries (1966-1969) (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Local 420 - Job specifications, salaries, contractetc., 1968; Publication (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: handwritten note - from Hospital Local 420, Publication (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Correspondence - The New York State Merger Convention - AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 340, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: For your information, 1952; Publication (Box 340, Folder 6)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Twelfth Annual State Convention, 1959; Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: News from AFSCME - Jerry Wurf; Joseph L. Ames; William Lucy; AFSCME, Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Welcome to the Michigan State Employees Union Council no. 7, Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Handbook of information for Local Union Officers - Michigan State Employees Union no. 7, 1958; Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Project Michigan, 1955; Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
    Notes: v. 1
  - Item 6: Project Michigan, 1956; Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
    Notes: v. 2, no. 3, 5-13, 16, 17 19- 24
  - Item 7: Bulletin, 1955-1956 (Box 340, Folder 7)
    Notes: no. 8-10
  - Item 8: Annual Convention, 1955; Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
    Notes: Oct. 1955
  - Item 9: Correspondence - Project Michigan, 1955; Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: Second Annual Report of the Director of ..., 1959; Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Second Annual Report of the Secretary-Treasurer, 1959; Publication (Box 340, Folder 7)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Official Program - NYS Convention, 1947; Publication (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Correspondence - from J. Howard DeGroff, Executive Secretary to employees, 1947; Publication (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: New York State Employees establish policy committees, plan legislation, 1945; Publication (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Legislation resolution, 1946; Publication (Box 340, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Report of Executive Secretary, 1946; Publication (Box 340, Folder 8)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: This is your union, State, county, and municipal workers of America (CIO), 1943; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Legal memorandum in support of power of municipalities to enter into collective agreements, 1942; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Labor for victory, 1943; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Facts about the trade union for public employees, Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Why industrial unionism for state, county & municipal workers?, 1939; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The rank and file movement in social work, 1931-1936, Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
    Author: Jacob Fisher
  - Item 7: OASI - a compilation of state and territorial enactments for the uses of old age and survivors insurance for public employees, 1956; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Its place its purpose, 1945; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Brief submitted to Mr. Milton O. Loysen, Executive Director for a Bureau-wide promotional plan for the Div. of Placement & Unemployment Insurance, 1940; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
    Author: Milton O. Loysen
  - Item 10: This is your union, Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: On public relations, 1947; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
    Author: Arnold S. Zander
    Notes: Article.
  - Item 12: News of State, County & Municipal Workers, 1944; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.11
  - Item 13: Librarian, 1944; Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
    Author: Lynn Aschbrenner
  - Item 14: Jim comes home smiling, Publication (Box 341, Folder 1)
- American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: While you're not looking, 1940; Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: What your taxes buy, 1948; Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Policemen have a constitutional right to form and join labor unions by Joseph A. Padway, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
    Author: Joseph A. Padway
  - Item 4: Public Servants, Organize!, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: What labor wants from Universities and what labor should do itself, 1954; Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
    Author: Joseph Mire
  - Item 6: We're all in the same boat, 1957; Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Comparative wage study of selected positions for New England States and New York, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Facts on AFSCME tour to Europe, 1955; Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Its place its purpose, 1946; Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Questions and answers (AFSCME), Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Symbol of better public service, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: A union for Hospital Workers, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: What can AFSCME do for me?, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Policemen have a constitutional right to form and join labor unions, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Application for charter, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Your local union membership is covered by Civil Service Provisions, Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: To his Majesty the "Cop", Publication (Box 341, Folder 2)